[♪ opening theme song playing]
[birds chirping]
[door opens]
-[Yuru gasps]
-[HANA] Come on in.
[Left and Right exclaim]
I wondered
what those stone castles
would look like from the inside.
Electricity and water
are already set up.
Somebody's gonna come by
to turn on the gas later.
[doorknob rattles]
[HANA] Dera, you can use
that Western-style room.
Yuru, you'll want
the tatami room, right?
Tatami? [gasps, exclaims]
This stuff's real!
Back in the village,
tatami are only used by Asa.
Or for very special events!
They usually use
goza mats, right?
Ah! [chuckles] They must have
a million layers,
with how thick each one feels!
We're living a life
of luxury here!
Are you sure I'm allowed
to sleep in this room?
-[footsteps]
-Hm?
[smacking]
[Yuru screams]
[HANA] Oh, that's my bad!
Let me introduce you.
This is Kotetsu and Jiro!
-[chuckles]
-[YURU] Mm?
Excuse the intrusion.
[Yuru gasps]
Our gratitude for letting
our master into your home!
And we're the daemons
contracted to him.
My name is Right. [chuckles]
And mine is Left.
Good health to you both.
-[KOTETSU] My man.
-[Jiro exclaims]
[DERA] Are those Hana's daemons?
Nice to finally meet you.
What? Those two are daemons?
That cat and dog?
[Yuru screams, grunts]
[RIGHT] They're not
your average cat and dog.
Now show some respect
and give 'em a proper greeting,
young one.
You put 'em together,
they're called Zenko-Koro.
-[Yuru whimpers]
-[HANA] Say hi!
Apologies.
[YURU] Hello.
[YURU] Danno?
I feel like we should use
my family name,
since somebody
let his identity slip.
Yeah, sorry. Good call.
[HANA] If anyone asks,
this is also your name.
Wait, you both have
family names?
Do you come from royalty?
Have I been disrespectful
to you, too?
Relax, kid. Everyone down here
has a last name.
Don't be fooled.
She owns a mountain!
She's a lord?
It's just something that got
passed down from my family!
There's no one maintaining it,
so it's an overgrown mess.
But I can't exactly
sell it, either.
[YURU] So, may I go
hunting there?
[Hana sighs] Don't say that
like it's normal.
[DERA] Down here, you need
to have a license to hunt.
-[YURU] Why?
-[DERA] Hey, you just do.
You'll need a separate one
if you wanna drive
those metal horses, too.
[YURU] This world
has so many rules.
♪
[ASA] Hmm.
[Asa grunts]
[Asa groans]
Still struggling to tune it.
-[GONZO] Hm.
-[Asa gasps]
[GONZO] Look at you,
hard at work!
[ASA] Master, you're back!
Yup!
[ASA] My apologies.
I brought harm
to your land again.
My accuracy still needs
improvement.
Oh, it's just a yard.
It's not as if
you killed anyone.
Keep trying,
and you'll get there.
Now, Jin, clean that up for us.
Yes, sir.
Ai, my dear?
[Ai growls]
Is there a reason
you came to visit?
Hm. Got a "get better" gift
for Gabby! [chuckles]
What?
You don't need to waste
your time worrying 'bout me.
How are you feeling, sweetie?
[GABBY] Not half bad.
Thanks for askin'.
And how are you holding up,
Gabriel?
[Gabriel grunts]
Hm. Yes. Of course, of course!
Hey, Gabby, you want
a little snack?
[GABBY] Apple me!
Oh, but I don't have a knife
to cut it the way you like.
Makoto.
[Makoto grunts]
For you.
Thanks to both of you.
How nice of you,
cutting up that apple with
a knife of dubious origin.
You really expect me
to eat that?
[JIN] It's all right.
It hasn't stabbed anyone.
Probably.
[GABBY] I am so reassured.
Now, Gabby, please focus
on rest and recovery.
[GABBY] 'Kay.
And as for you, Asa,
-I want you to stay with her.
-[ASA] Huh?
With you and your brother
both off the mountain,
it's safe to say word is gonna
start getting around fast.
That means people
will soon be after you.
Even just looking
within the Kagemori clan,
there are some
targeting you, I fear.
But as long as you're here,
I can keep you safe.
I've instructed Jin
to continue searching for Yuru.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
One small problem.
I don't even know what this
big brother looks like.
Ah... we should have snapped
a pic while we were there!
[scribbling]
-Here!
-[JIN] Seems biased.
-[Gabby yells]
-[JIN] Abstract.
Whoa, Flawless?
[clears throat]
I'll begin the search
by looking into Tadera.
Don't disappoint!
[footsteps]
[ASA] Before you go...
Is something wrong?
My brother's daemons
have keen noses.
-[JIN] Hm.
-They could identify me
from the smell of my blood.
[Jin gasps softly]
[JIN] Incredible.
[DERA] Oh, yeah!
I'm a new man!
Hold up. Where'd your beard go?
They saw my face,
so I had to shave it.
Every little bit,
to throw 'em off the scent!
You lost your only similarity
to Jason Statham.
You're dead to me now.
We just tied the knot,
and my wife's
already lost interest.
Do you know where our pride
and joy ran off to?
[HANA] If you're talking
about Yuru,
he said he was going for a walk
to get the lay of the land.
Think he'll be okay?
[HANA] He's got
Left and Right with him.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
[DERA] Hana,
where's my billhook?
[HANA] Don't ask me.
I didn't touch it.
[DERA] I'm sure
I left it by the door.
Ah, crap.
Wonder how far he went.
-[Hana grunts]
-If the cops find him,
he's in violation
of the Firearms
and Swords Control Act.
[HANA] I told him
to stay out of trouble!
I hate kids!
The world below sure is big.
The stars reach
all the way to the ground.
It's massive.
[RIGHT] Does the vastness
concern you?
Is it you fear
it will be impossible
to find a singular person
in this world?
I have no doubt
that your paths shall meet.
She's seeking you out as well.
[laughs]
How quaint!
Power of sibling love!
♪
Can't you sense daemons?
Like how you did before
with Oshirasama.
Was that just by smell?
Aye.
[YURU] And you said
this Asa's blood
smelled like mine?
Aye.
[YURU] Dera said the Kagemoris
have many daemon wielders.
Not just the runt.
So that's what
we're looking for.
A place with daemons
that smells of my blood, yeah?
That's enough to begin.
Let's go!
♪
[Right laughs]
[RIGHT] We'll up the sensitivity
a notch!
♪
[Yuru screams]
[Yuru screams, laughs]
[Yuru shouts indistinctly]
[Yuru vomits, coughs]
[Yuru whimpers]
Blood like yours and daemons.
I believe we have unearthed
-a perfect match.
-[Yuru groans]
There's daemons here?
You're sure?
Have we permission
to cut them down
should they dare
to show themselves?
Shouldn't we at least
try to speak with them first,
in case they're friendly
like Oshirasama?
You'd be wise
not to measure daemons
by the same standards as humans.
We're too varied
to relate to one another.
Some have no means
to process reason.
Interesting.
So I should think of them
like bears, or wild boar.
[RIGHT] Simpleton.
Huh? [sniffs]
[YURU] Hm?
♪
[JIN] You found it?
Ah, I see.
Then I'm sure Mr. Tadera
must have already
cleared out the space.
Yep.
I want to be the first to know
if you hear anything.
Ah, the smell of Asa
is only matched
by the smell of those
daemons of theirs.
Though, we must be sure
to stay on our guard.
If we've noticed them,
no doubt they've caught
wind of us, too.
-[RIGHT] See anything?
-[YURU] No, nothing.
Those guys in black are humans,
right?
[RIGHT] Seem to be.
-[Right sniffs]
-[LEFT] Hm?
♪
[Yuru gasps]
[Yuru grunts]
Asa!
Wait, Yuru!
The blood's scent is aged!
She's not...
According to my sources,
your daemons have
a strong sense of smell.
Furthermore, since you reacted
so strongly to this Asa...
it seems I've caught
her brother.
How do you do, kid?
The name's Jin Kagemori.
These here are my daemons,
the Scavenger.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance, Yuru.
[Yuru grunts softly]
[HANA] Shit. Shit, shit, shit!
We gotta find out
where Yuru is ASAP.
[DERA] I'd say so.
He still doesn't know
the ways of our world,
so he might wind up
hurting someone.
-[Hana grunts]
-[Dera gasps]
[HANA] That's just one problem.
But what are we gonna do
if he's the one who gets hurt?
Wait, what happened
to Miss Hates-Children?
Seems like you're
awfully worried
about how our boy's doing!
[HANA] What?
Are you willfully ignorant,
or dumb?
-[DERA] Huh?
-[HANA] Last I checked,
the kid isn't
a registered citizen yet.
Yeah, obviously.
His hometown
is a bit behind the times.
Hold on.
Doesn't that mean...
[BOTH] He's got
no health insurance.
So we're on the hook
for any medical bills!
-Shit, shit, shit...
-Jiro.
[Jiro barks]
This thing ought
to smell like Yuru.
-Let's track him down!
-[Jiro sniffs]
[Jiro grunts]
We're counting on you!
[Jiro barking]
[Jiro howls]
[HANA] Kotetsu, your turn.
[Kotetsu grunts]
Well, would you look at that.
Your daemons can use
modern tech?
[HANA] They adapted
to living around here.
They've been in my family
for generations,
so it was bound to happen.
So then? Where did our
good boy run off to?
Huh?
How the hell did he get
all the way to Tokyo
in one night?
Damn, kid. Wasting no time.
[HANA] Left and Right
must've taken him.
[DERA] Is he lost?
No. Maybe he had a good reason
to go there.
♪
[JIN] You may think we're crazy
for chasing you twins,
but the Higashi Village elders
are just as bad.
That said, they're recovering
from our attack,
and you're freshly on the run,
so things are peaceful.
Surely they wouldn't stage
a counterattack already.
But I'm sure they know
we're thinking that
and expect us
to let down our guard.
I couldn't rule it out.
So I laid this trap
for one of them to fall into.
The fact we got you was lucky.
Thanks for that,
Mr. Big Brother.
[Yuru grunts]
[YURU] Too tough.
Hey, daemons,
you're hiding, right?
Come on out.
Thoughts, Left?
I don't detect the scent of iron
wafting off them.
It would appear this lot
is unarmed, at least.
Though I do still sense
their daemons.
The fish and four more.
The other pairs
must belong to them.
They're hiding until
we make the first move,
waiting to see what we do.
[both grunt softly]
[Right grunts]
[RIGHT] Oh, well.
Whatever happens happens.
[HARUO] There, look!
Stay right where you are!
We will kill your master
if you do not comply!
We're happy to give him back,
as long as you guys... [gasps]
Hey, stop!
Hey! Are you listening to me?
Don't you dare come any closer!
I'm telling you
your master is our hostage!
And which one should be
our hostage?
The sullen one.
Seems he's in charge.
[HARUO] Come on, guys!
I said stop!
My apologies, you two.
I lost my head back there.
[RIGHT] Eh, can't blame you
for that one.
Just be sure to stay put.
Mm? Why should I?
This fish thing looks powerful.
As long as it's busy
being your jail cell,
it can't fight us.
Oh. I can accept that.
Works for me.
What did they say?
Why are the daemons
giving orders to their master?
You guys are
supposed to prioritize
rescuing your master
over everything else!
[YURU] Nah,
I'm pretty hands-off.
[laughs] You've got your way,
we've got ours!
Remember, our opponents
have no weapons.
We should take it easy on them.
I ought to be the one
telling you that.
But sure.
Give us a hand.
[Yuru gasps]
[YURU] Careful of those weapons.
[Jin grunts softly]
[RIGHT] Huh?
You bid us be careful of what?
We're sculpted of stone,
far tougher than that.
[chuckles awkwardly]
Yeah, of course.
How annoying.
What do you suppose these are?
They remind me of matchlocks.
♪
[Haruo grunts]
[grunts] Keep tryin'.
It ain't workin'.
[Makoto grunts]
[Right grunts]
[LEFT] Was that a lantern?
Actually,
they're quite well-armed.
Don't gotta hold back.
Agreed.
Aw, crap. Out of the way, Akio!
I got you!
You all right?
[Right grunting]
[Right grunts]
What's going on?
Come on, Left, help me!
[LEFT] Apologies, Right. Busy.
I can't move.
'Tis heavy.
'Tis so very heavy.
Truly? [screams]
Please save me, Left!
[LEFT] I cannot. Save yourself.
♪
[Yuru grunts softly]
[Yuru grunts]
[YURU] That's it.
Yuru, stay clear!
[Ai screams]
Less tough than the other teeth.
[Yuru grunts]
Right!
When you leave the latrine, you?
[Right grunts]
[RIGHT] Kill the lights!
-[BUNBUN] Haruo, where are you?
-Over here.
I sense the boy's daemons moving
further away from us
with each passing second.
[HARUO] They got away?
[JIN] No. Akio's daemons
are lying in wait.
If you think
you're getting away that easy,
you're dead wrong.
You should see him.
He's got the mind
of a die-hard hunter!
[Jin grunts softly]
-[whooshes]
-[Jin grunts]
[grunts] Makoto, light!
♪
[Jin breathes uneasily]
-Oy! Did it work out?
-[Haruo gasps] Hey!
What's your deal?
Daemons shouldn't abandon
their master! You ran!
[RIGHT] Bah...
I don't know what you guys do,
but this is what we've found
works for us.
We may do as we please
as long as the job gets done.
Huh? Doesn't it make sense
to run away from a trap
when you can?
Better than all dying.
Uh, suppose you have a point.
Your surprise makes me think
you've forgotten.
But of the twins,
our Yuru commands the night.
[LEFT] The darkness
is his hunting ground.
He can manage fine without us.
[Haruo gasps]
I totally love how much faith
you have in him.
That rocks.
Had Yuru failed to secure
his prey, though,
we would have swept in
to assist him.
Even in the murk,
we can track your scent.
Only natural.
You grew up in
a mountain village, after all.
In a battle of senses,
you have an undeniable advantage
over us.
You said you're a Kagemori.
Is your clan responsible
for the attack on Higashi?
[JIN] I alone am responsible.
-[both gasp]
-No, don't!
♪
[breathing shakily]
[Yuru sighs]
[YURU] You've got one of those
smoke signal things, right?
[JIN] Hm?
The device that lets you talk
to people far away.
I saw you were using it earlier.
Oh, you mean my smartphone.
You're gonna tell Asa
to come here.
I just want to talk, that's all.
[♪ closing theme song playing]
Gabby! Gabby! Gabby!
Jin is bringing
my brother here.
Our parents boarded
the plane to Okinawa,
but didn't land.
They're gone.